A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 1, Accession 2017:057 FA1317
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1966-1999; 3
  - Chinese Histories in the United States, 1983-1994 (Box 47, Folder 348-349)
  - Chinese Histories in the United States (Renewal), 1989 (Box 48, Folder 350)
  - Chinese Histories in the United States - Chairman's Award: Teaching Project in China, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 351)
  - Chinese People's Association for Friendship with Foreign Countries, 1988-1995 (Box 48, Folder 352)
  - Chinese People's University, Beijing - Eminent Chinese of the China Period, 1989-1991 (Box 48, Folder 353)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong - Chinese Studies, 1974-1994 (Box 48, Folder 354)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - President's Grant, 1988-1992 (Box 48, Folder 355)
  - The Chrysler Museum - Myth, Magic, and Mystery, 1994-1997 (Box 48, Folder 356)
  - Cities in Schools (New York) - 1990 Summer Program, 1988-1992 (Box 48, Folder 357)
  - City University of New York - Graduate School and University Center - Chairman Grant: Adjunct Professor in Art History, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 358)
  - Claremont Colleges - Oral Histories: Chinese Missionaries, 1968-1977 (Box 84, Folder 631)
  - Claremont University Center and Graduate School, 1985-1989 (Box 27, Folder 208)
  - The College of Wooster, 1980-1990 (Box 27, Folder 209-210, Box 84, Folder 632)
  - The College of Wooster - Dormitory, 1988-1995 (Box 49, Folder 359-360)
  - The College of Wooster - Leadership and Liberal Learning, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 361)
  - The College of Wooster - Research and Study Leave Program, 1969-1972 (Box 85, Folder 633)
  - College Placement Services, 1969-1970 (Box 85, Folder 634)
  - The Colorado College - Thomas Cronin, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 362-363)
  - The Colorado College- Religion and Spirituality Symposium, 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 364)
  - Columbia Theological Seminary, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 365)
  - Columbia University - Andrew Nathan, 1986-1992 (Box 27, Folder 211)
  - Columbia University - Center for United States-China Arts Exchange, 1986-1991 (Box 27, Folder 212, Box 28, Folder 213-219)
  - Columbia University - Chairman's Award: deBarry Chair in Oriental Cultures, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 367)
  - Columbia University - East Asian Institute, 1985-1993 (Box 28, Folder 220)
  - Columbia University - East Asian Institute - Undergraduate Curriculum, 1986-1993 (Box 29, Folder 221)
  - Columbia University - Maurice T. Moore Professorship, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 222)
  - Columbia University - Teacher's College Minority Leadership, 1988-1993 (Box 50, Folder 366)
  - Columbus Museum of Art - Folk Artist Elijah Pierce, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 368-369)
  - Committee on International Relations - Studies with the PRC (CIRSPRC) (IIE), 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 223)
  - Committee on International Relations Studies with China - Institute of International Education (IIE), 1988-1991 (Box 50, Folder 370)
  - Committe on Legal Education Exchanges with the PRC, 1983-1995 (Box 51, Folder 371-372)
  - Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China, 1990-1998 (Box 51, Folder 373)
  - Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China - National Academy of Sciences, 1984-1989 (Box 29, Folder 224)
  - Connecticut College - International Studies in Liberal Arts, 1988-1990 (Box 51, Folder 374)
  - Consortium for Graduate Study in Managment, 1968-1972 (Box 85, Folder 635-636)
  - Cornell University - Leslie Severinghaus Research Room, 1989-1992 (Box 51, Folder 375)
  - Cornell University - Southeast Asian Studies Summer Institute (SEASSI), 1989-1991 (Box 51, Folder 376)
  - The Coro Foundation, 1980-1982 (Box 85, Folder 637)
  - The Council of Churches of the City of New York, 1988-1992 (Box 52, Folder 377)
  - Council of Protestant Colleges and Universities, 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 638)
  - Council on Legal Education Opportunities (CLEO), 1968-1970 (Box 85, Folder 639)
  - Dallas Museum of Art - American Art, 1985-1991 (Box 29, Folder 225-226)
  - DIA Center for the Arts - Brice Marden Project, 1991-1994 (Box 52, Folder 378)
  - Dominion College - Purchase of Library Books, 1995-1996 (Box 52, Folder 379)
  - The Door, 1986-1994 (Box 29, Folder 227-228)
  - The Door - College Preparation, 1982-1992 (Box 52, Folder 380)
  - The Drawing Center, 1989-1995 (Box 52, Folder 381-382)
  - The Drawing Center - Plains Indian Ledger Drawings, 1994-199 (Box 53, Folder 383-384)
  - Duke University - Leadership Program, 1987-1993 (Box 53, Folder 385-386)
  - East Asian History of Science, Inc., 1984-1990 (Box 30, Folder 229)
  - East-West Center, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 230-231)
  - East-West Center - New Generation Seminar for Asian Women, 1990-1992 (Box 53, Folder 387)
  - East-West Center - President's Grant: Annual Membership Campaign, 1989-1992 (Box 53, Folder 388)
  - East-West Philosophical Conference, 1968-1976 (Box 86, Folder 640)
  - Eastern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1981-1992 (Box 30, Folder 232, Box 53, Folder 389)
  - Edgehill Church - Chairman's Grant: The Living Pulpit Magazine, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 390)
  - Educational Policy Center, 1971-1973 (Box 86, Folder 641)
  - Educational Testing Service - ISSP, 1968-1973 (Box 86, Folder 642-643)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, 1971-1991 (Box 30, Folder 233-234)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, Inc. - Fellows from India, 1989-1992 (Box 54, Folder 391)
  - Emory University - Presidential Award - Jonas Robitscher Lectureship in Law and Psychiatry, 1984-1993 (Box 30, Folder 235)
  - Episcopal Church at Yale - Development, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 392)
  - Executive Council on Foreign Diplomats, Inc., 1979-1983 (Box 86, Folder 644)
  - Federation for American Immigration Reform - Chairman's Award: Dr. Katharine Betts College Seminar, 1991-1992 (Box 54, Folder 393)
  - Federation for American Immigration - President's Grant: Startup Costs and Intern Stipend, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Folder 394)
  - Federation for American Immigration Reform - Study on Issues in United States Immigration Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 54, Folder 395)
  - The Film History Foundation - The China Call, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 396)
  - The Fine Arts Museum of San Francisco, 1988-1995 (Box 54, Folder 397)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1986-1993 (Box 31, Folder 236)
  - Fordham University, 1983-1988 (Box 31, Folder 237)
  - Fordham University - Music and Poetry (Renewal), 1980-1988 (Box 31, Folder 238)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1992-1995 (Box 54, Folder 398)
  - 42nd Street Development Corp., 1980-1991 (Box 31, Folder 239)
  - The Foundation Center, 1988-1995 (Box 31, Folder 240, Box 54, Folder 399-400)
  - The Foundation for Books to China, 1984-1989 (Box 31, Folder 241)
  - Foundation for the Preforming Arts - Colleen Moore Memorial Fund, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 401)
  - Foundation for Student Communication - Target Education, 1993-1996 (Box 54, Folder 402)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - Chairman's Grant: International Economic Diplomacy, 1991-1995 (Box 55, Folder 403)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - Economics for Leaders Program, 1991-1995 (Box 55, Folder 404)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - President's Award: Annual Report to Targeted Professionals, 1990-1995 (Box 55, Folder 405)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - President's Grant, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 406)
  - Foundation for Theological Education - History of Christian Thought, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 407)
  - Freer Art Gallery - Harmony in Blue and Gold: Peacock Room, 1991-1999 (Box 55, Folder 408-409)
  - Friends of Sarospatak Academy - Presidential Award: Worldwide Christian Schools, 1990-1993 (Box 55, Folder 410)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary, 1992-1997 (Box 55, Folder 411)
  - Fund for Theological Education, 1983-1991 (Box 32, Folder 242)
  - Fundamentalists Anonymous, 1985-1992 (Box 32, Folder 243)
  - Fundamentalists Anonymous - Chairman's Award: Loan Repayment, 1992-1996 (Box 55, Folder 412)
  - Fundamentalists Anonymous - Leadership Training, 1988-1993 (Box 59, Folder 435-436)
  - Sidney D. Gamble Foundation for China Studies, 1988-1995 (Box 56, Folder 413)
  - The Garden Conservancy - Chairman's Award, 1993-1998 (Box 56, Folder 414)
  - General Theological Seminary - Center for Christian Spirituality, 1989-1994 (Box 56, Folder 415)
  - Georgetown University - Clare Boothe Luce Room, 1989-1991 (Box 56, Folder 416)
  - Georgetown University - President's Award: Dean Peter Krogh Excellence Award, 1990-1995 (Box 56, Folder 417)
  - The Governance Institute, 1987-1989 (Box 56, Folder 418-419)
  - Global Forum of Spiritual and Parliamentary Leaders, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 420)
  - Goshen College, 1986-1991 (Box 32, Folder 244)
  - Grace Bible Chapel, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 421)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Buddhist Christian Conference, 1986-1989 (Box 32, Folder 245)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Catalog, Registrar, 1968-1972 (Box 86, Folder 645)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Faculty Studies in Pacific and Asian Cultures, 1990-1995 (Box 57, Folder 422-423)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Harvard Divinity School, 1979-1984 (Box 86, Folder 646)
  - Graduate Theological Union - New Religious Movements, 1980-1987 (Box 86, Folder 647)
  - Group of Thirty, 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 648)
  - Guggenheim Museum, 1986-1994 (Box 32, Folder 246-247)
  - Armand Hammer Museum - Pacific Dreams: Early California Art, 1994-1998 (Box 57, Folder 424-425)
  - Harvard University - Divinity School: Post-Doctoral Fellows Program (Renewal), 1990-1997 (Box 57, Folder 426)
  - Harvard University - Fairbank Center, 1988-1991 (Box 57, Folder 427)
  - Harvard University - Film Archive, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 428)
  - Harvard University - Fine Arts Library, 1987-1991 (Box 58, Folder 429)
  - Harvard University - Graduate School of Education, 1968-1976 (Box 87, Folder 649)
  - Harvard University - Institute for International Development, 1991-1996 (Box 58, Folder 430)
  - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government Leadership, 1988-1995 (Box 58, Folder 431-432)
  - Harvard University - Theodore H. White Lectureship, 1989-1996 (Box 58, Folder 433)
  - The Hastings Center, 1979-1994 (Box 32, Folder 248-249, Box 33, Folder 250, Box 58, Folder 434)
  - The Healthcare Chaplaincy, 1990-1996 (Box 59, Folder 437)
  - Henry Street Settlement, 1986-1996 (Box 33, Folder 251, Box 59, Folder 438)
  - The High Museum of Art, 1986-1993 (Box 59, Folder 439)
  - The High Museum of Art - Catalog of American Art Collection, 1990-1995 (Box 59, Folder 440)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 1993-1999 (Box 60, Folder 441-442)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 443)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts - Encounters with Paradise: Views of Hawaii Exhibition, 1987-1992 (Box 60, Folder 444)
  - The Horticultural Society of New York - The Harlem Project, 1992-1995 (Box 60, Folder 445)
  - The Hospital Chaplaincy, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 252)
  - The Hospital Chaplaincy - Theology, 1987-1990 (Box 60, Folder 446)
  - Howard University - Divinity School, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 253)
  - Independent Curators Incorporated, 1986-1992 (Box 33, Folder 254, Box 60, Folder 447-448)
  - Independent Sector, 1980-1996 (Box 61, Folder 449, Box 87, Folder 650-651)
  - Institute for Advanced Study, 1989-1994 (Box 61, Folder 450)
  - Institute for International Education, 1988-1993 (Box 61, Folder 451)
  - Institute of International Education - Chiangmei Conference, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 655)
  - Institute of International Education - Dinner Honoring Elisabeth Luce Moore, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 461)
  - Institute of International Education - Foreign Leadership Intern Project, 1969-1972 (Box 87, Folder 656, Box 88, Folder 657)
  - Institute of International Education - Guangzhou Center (Renewal), 1987-1990 (Box 61, Folder 452)
  - Institute of International Education - Hong Kong Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 88, Folder 658-659)
  - Institute of International Education - Jogjakarta Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 660-661)
  - Institute of International Education - Manila Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 88, Folder 662)
  - Institute of International Education - Nara Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 663)
  - Institute of International Education - Sapporo Conference, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 664)
  - Institutes of Religion and Health, 1987-1991 (Box 61, Folder 453)
  - Institutes of Religion and Health - Urban Ministries Program, 1991-1996 (Box 61, Folder 454)
  - Interdenominational Theological Center - World Religions Program (Renewal), 1990-1999 (Box 62, Folder 455-456)
  - Interfaith Forum on Religion, Art, and Architecture, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 457)
  - The International Center, 1987-1990 (Box 62, Folder 458)
  - International Center in New York - Restructuring English as Second Language Program, 1990-1997 (Box 62, Folder 459-460)
  - International Council for Education Development, 1980-1987 (Box 87, Folder 652)
  - International Foundation for Art Research (IFAR) - Development Efforts, 1990-1992 (Box 63, Folder 462)
  - International Foundation for EWHA Woman's University - Chairman Grant: Visiting Scholars Lectureship, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder 463)
  - International Institute for Environmental Affairs, 1971-1974 (Box 89, Folder 665-666)
  - International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1979-1987 (Box 87, Folder 654)
  - International Institute of Rural Reconstruction, 1980-1984 (Box 87, Folder 653)
  - International Institute of Rural Reconstruction - Catalog: Jimmy Yen's Papers at Columbia University's Asian Library, 1991-1998 (Box 63, Folder 464)
  - International Leadership Center - Leadership America, 1987-1989 (Box 63, Folder 465-466)
  - International Leadership Center - Leadership America (Renewal), 1988-1990 (Box 63, Folder 467)
  - International Leadership Center Foundation - President's Grant:Leadership in America Class, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 468)
  - International Myeloma Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 469)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity (ICBO) - Newark Project, 1970-1972 (Box 89, Folder 667)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange, 1987-1991 (Box 63, Folder 470)
  - Japan Society, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box 89, Folder 668-669)
  - John LaFarge Institute - John Courtney Murray Forum, 1968-1972 (Box 89, Folder 670)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 471)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Nanjing Center: English Language and Library, 1989-1999 (Box 64, Folder 472)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS) Graduate Interns, 1971-1976 (Box 90, Folder 671)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Southeast Asian Studies, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 473)
  - Knoxville College, 1968-1976 (Box 90, Folder 672-673)
  - Library of Congress - Southeast Asia Cooperative Acquisitions, 1989-1995 (Box 64, Folder 474)
  - Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church - David Reed Preacher-Scholar Scholarship Fund, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 475)
  - Marietta College - Issues of Leadership Pedagogy, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 476)
  - Marietta College - McDonough Center for Leadership, 1990-1993 (Box 64, Folder 477)
  - Marymount Manhattan College - Chairman's Award: President's Medal to Aileen Mehle, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 478)
  - McCormick Theological Seminary - Leadership Education in Korean-American Community in the Mid-West, 1991-1994 (Box 64, Folder 479)
  - Meharry Medical College, 1971-1978 (Box 90, Folder 674)
  - Memorial Art Gallery of the University of Rochester - Elbert Hubbard and the Roycrofters, 1990-1997 (Box 65, Folder 480)
  - Mepkin Abbey - Garden Renovations, 1987-1993 (Box 65, Folder 481)
  - Metro International - Development Efforts, 1991-1994 (Box 65, Folder 482-483)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - American Rococo, 1750-1775: Elegance in Ornament, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 484)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Chairman's Award: Douglass Fleming, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 485)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Stuart Davis, 1989-1992 (Box 65, Folder 486)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - "Harlem on my Mind", 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 675)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - "Harlem on my Mind" Letters, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 676)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - "Harlem on my Mind" Press Clippings, 1967-1969 (Box 90, Folder 677, Box 91, Folder 678)
  - The Micronesia Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 487)
  - The Micronesia Institute - Follow-through Grant, 1991-1996 (Box 66, Folder 488-489)
  - The Micronesia Institute - President's Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 490-491)
  - The Micronesia Institute - President's Grant:Endowment for Historic Preservation, 1990-1992 (Box 66, Folder 492)
  - Milton Art Museum - President's Grant: Beth Neville Exhibit, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 493)
  - Ministry in the North Country - Internship for David Frederickson, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 494)
  - Minneapolis Institute of Arts - Plains and Woodland Indian Painting, 1990-1993 (Box 67, Folder 495-496)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1989-1994 (Box 67, Folder 497)
  - Municipal Art Society, 1987-1991 (Box 67, Folder 498)
  - Munson- Williams Proctor Institute - Life Lines: American Master Drawings, 1993-1997 (Box 67, Folder 499)
  - Museum of American Folk Art - Thorton Dial, 1990-1991 (Box 68, Folder 500-501)
  - Museum of the City of New York - President's Grant: Printed Guide to the Museum, 1990-1991 (Box 68, Folder 502)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art - Ad Reinhardt Exhibit, 1981-1992 (Box 68, Folder 503-504)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art - Robert Irwin Retrospective, 1991-1994 (Box 68, Folder 505)
  - Museum of Fine Arts (Boston) - Americans in Italy, 1991-1996 (Box 69, Folder 506)
  - Museum of Fine Arts (Boston) - American Paintings Catalog, 1987-1993 (Box 69, Folder 507)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1968-1972 (Box 69, Folder 508)
  - National Association of Independent Schools, 1969-1979 (Box 69, Folder 509-510)
  - National Catholic Education Association, 1969-1973 (Box 69, Folder 511)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations, 1979-1981 (Box 70, Folder 512)
  - National Dance Institute - Administration Reorganization, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 513)
  - National Dance Institute - "Faces in the Sky", 1994 (Box 70, Folder 514)
  - National Manpower Institute, 1971-1977 (Box 70, Folder 515)
  - National Opinion Research Center (University of Chicago), 1971-1974 (Box 70, Folder 516)
  - National Presbyterian Church and Center, 1968-1975 (Box 70, Folder 517)
  - National Urban League, 1969-1974 (Box 71, Folder 518-521)
  - National Urban League - Development Capability Enhancement, 1989-1998 (Box 71, Folder 522-523)
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art - Chairman's Award: Vera List Challenge, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 524)
  - New York Historical Society - Golden Family Foundation Loan, 1992-1994 (Box 72, Folder 525)
  - New York Theological Seminary, 1969-1981 (Box 72, Folder 526-527)
  - New York Urban Coalition, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 528)
  - Nieman Endowment Fund, 1967-1972 (Box 72, Folder 529)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art - Louis Remy Mignot, 1992-1998 (Box 72, Folder 530-532)
  - Open Space Institute - Sustainable Development Institute, 1993-1996 (Box 73, Folder 533)
  - Opera Music Theatre International - Chairman's Award: Dong-Jian Gong Fellowship, 1991-1995 (Box 73, Folder 534)
  - Opera Music Theatre International - Fellowships for Jing-Ma Fan, 1992-1995 (Box 73, Folder 535)
  - Opera Music Theatre International - Showcase Concert, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 536)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Centers of America, 1968-1976 (Box 73, Folder 537)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Center (OIC) of New York, 1968-1972 (Box 73, Folder 538)
  - Overseas Development Council, 1980-1985 (Box 73, Folder 539)
  - Pacific Theological College - Lotu: History of Christianity in the Pacific, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 540)
  - Palace of Governors History Museum - "Friends of the Palace", 1993-1995 (Box 73, Folder 541-542)
  - Pan American Development Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 73, Folder 543)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City - Hub Program, 1991-1995 (Box 74, Folder 544-545)
  - Potomac Associates, 1979-1986 (Box 74, Folder 546)
  - Presbyterian Church, USA - Moscow Protestant Chaplaincy, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 547)
  - Preservation Society of Newport County - Newport Symposium Filming, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 548)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Concillium: International Theological Review, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 549)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Hillel and Jesus Symposium, Jerusalem, 1992-1997 (Box 74, Folder 550)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Library Expansion, 1988-1993 (Box 74, Folder 551-552)
  - Regional Plan Association - Pedestrian Study, 1968-1982 (Box 75, Folder 553)
  - Reynolda House Museum of American Art - Academic Affairs, 1992-1997 (Box 75, Folder 554-555)
  - Save Amateur Sports, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 556)
  - St. Bernard's School - Classroom and Library Building, 1967-1970 (Box 75, Folder 557)
  - St. John's College - Graduate Institute of Liberal Education, 1971-1980 (Box 75, Folder 558)
  - St. Thomas the Apostle Church, 1968-1970 (Box 75, Folder 559)
  - Seven Theological Schools Project - Yale Divinity School, 1970-1974 (Box 75, Folder 560)
  - Society for the Arts, Religion and Contemporary Culture, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 561)
  - Society for the Arts, Religion and Contemporary Culture - Executive Director, 1968-1972 (Box 76, Folder 562)
  - Society of Women Geographers, 1992-1995 (Box 76, Folder 563-564)
  - Southeast Asian Ministers of Education Secretariat, 1971-1974 (Box 76, Folder 565)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) - Center for Advanced Religious Studies (Stony Brook), 1978-1985 (Box 76, Folder 566)
  - Student-Sponsor Partnership (Renewal), 1993-1996 (Box 76, Folder 567)
  - Trilateral Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 76, Folder 568)
  - Urban America, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 569)
  - University of California, Davis - Late Ming Religion and Culture in Christian Perspective, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 570)
  - University of California, Davis - President's Grant: "Confucian Christians", 1990-1995 (Box 77, Folder 571)
  - University of Chicago - Divinity School, 1980-1987 (Box 77, Folder 572)
  - Venture in Mission, 1979-1981 (Box 77, Folder 573)
  - Vietnam Veterans of America, 1979-1981 (Box 77, Folder 574)
  - Wake Forest University, 1979-1985 (Box 77, Folder 575)
  - Wellesley College - MIT Cross Registration, 1967-1973 (Box 77, Folder 576-577)
  - Wesleyan University - Young Organ Virtuosi Presentations, 1993-1995 (Box 78, Folder 578)
  - Williams College, 1979-1982 (Box 78, Folder 579)
  - Williams College - James A. Linen III - Fund for Asian Studies, 1993-1996 (Box 78, Folder 580)
  - Williams College Museum of Art - The Art of Maurice Brazil Pendergast, 1990-1992 (Box 78, Folder 581-582)
  - The Williamsburg Charter Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 78, Folder 583)
  - The Williamsburg Charter Foundation - President's Grant: Termination Costs, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 584)
  - The Woodrow Wilson Center - Priorities in China Studies, 1987-1990 (Box 78, Folder 585)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Smithsonian), 1977-1979 (Box 79, Folder 586)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 79, Folder 587-588)
  - Thomas Waterman Wood Art Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 79, Folder 589)
  - World Monuments Fund - American Heritage Sites: St. Anne's Church, 1988-1991 (Box 79, Folder 590)
  - World Monuments Fund - Restoration of Spanish Colonial Adobe Churches of New Mexico, 1991-1994 (Box 79, Folder 591)
  - World Peace through Law Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 592)
  - Yale-China Association, 1990-1993 (Box 80, Folder 593)
  - Yale Institute of Sacred Music, 1980-1988 (Box 80, Folder 594)
  - Yale University, 1988-1994 (Box 80, Folder 595)